{"title": ["Verb to be: am/is/are", "Possessive adjectives: my, your, his, her", "Subject Pronouns - Plural nouns & Numbers"], "count": 44, "Question0": {"question": "A- Hello, what ______ your name?", "example": ["A) is ", "B) are ", "C) am ", "D) be"], "answer": "A"}, "Question1": {"question": "______ name is John. And my ______ is Johnson.", "example": ["A) Your / surname ", "B) My / surname", "C) I / surname ", "D) I / name"], "answer": "B"}, "Question2": {"question": "My name is Lisa. ______ Lisa Peterson.", "example": ["A) My am ", "B) I is ", "C) I am ", "D) I"], "answer": "C"}, "Question3": {"question": "______ name is Apple. ______ Ann Apple.", "example": ["A) His / She ", "B) His / He\u2019s ", "C) Her / She\u2019s ", "D) His / His"], "answer": "C"}, "Question4": {"question": "\u201cWhere ______ John from?\u201d \u201c______ from the US.\u201d", "example": ["A) is / He\u2019s ", "B) is / His ", "C) am / He\u2019s ", "D) is / She\u2019s"], "answer": "A"}, "Question5": {"question": "______ are you from? Japan.", "example": ["A) What ", "B) Who ", "C) Where ", "D) When"], "answer": "C"}, "Question6": {"question": "Where ______ you ______ ?", "example": ["A) is / from ", "B) are / in ", "C) are / is ", "D) are / from"], "answer": "D"}, "Question7": {"question": "______ from Spain. I\u2019m Rodriguez .", "example": ["A) I\u2019m ", "B) He\u2019s ", "C) You\u2019re ", "D) She\u2019s"], "answer": "A"}, "Question8": {"question": "Pierre is a French boy. ______ from ______ .", "example": ["A) He\u2019s / France ", "B) His\u2019s / French", "C) His / France ", "D) He / France"], "answer": "A"}, "Question9": {"question": "Lisa and Max are Americans. ______ from U.S.A.", "example": ["A) There ", "B) Their ", "C) They\u2019re ", "D) Their\u2019re"], "answer": "C"}, "Question10": {"question": "\u201cWhat ____ their _____?\u201d / \u201cAlexander and Philip.\u201d", "example": ["A) are/name ", "B) is / name ", "C) is / names ", "D) are / names"], "answer": "D"}, "Question11": {"question": "I ______ 22 years old, but Andrew ______ 20.", "example": ["A) am / am ", "B) are / am ", "C) am / is ", "D) are / are"], "answer": "C"}, "Question12": {"question": "Mark______ 19, but Brian and Denis ______ 26 and 28.", "example": ["A) is / are ", "B) are / is ", "C) are / are ", "D) am / are"], "answer": "A"}, "Question13": {"question": "\u201cWhat ______ this?\u201d / \u201cIt\u2019s ______ umbrella.\u201d", "example": ["A) are / a ", "B) is / a ", "C) is / an ", "D) its / an"], "answer": "C"}, "Question14": {"question": "Oxford is ______ English university.", "example": ["A) an ", "B) the ", "C) a ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question15": {"question": "Toyotas ______ Japanese ______ .", "example": ["A) is a / car ", "B) is / car ", "C) are / cars ", "D) is / cars"], "answer": "C"}, "Question16": {"question": "\u201cWhat is ______ ?\u201d / \u201cShe is a bank manager.\u201d", "example": ["A) his job ", "B)she job ", "C) he job ", "D) her job"], "answer": "D"}, "Question17": {"question": "0/2/11/18/20 Find the correct alternative.", "example": ["A) oh / twelve / eighteen / twenty", "B) zero / two / one-one / eighteen / twenty", "C) zero / two / eleven / eighteen / twenty", "D) zero / two / eleven / eighty / twenty"], "answer": "C"}, "Question18": {"question": "\u201cHow old is your aunt?\u201d / \u201c______ is 29.\u201d", "example": ["A) She ", "B) He ", "C) She\u2019s ", "D) He\u2019s"], "answer": "C"}, "Question19": {"question": "\u201cWhere ______ she from?\u201d / \u201cShe ______ from Japan.\u201d", "example": ["A) are / is ", "B) is / is ", "C) is / am ", "D) are / are"], "answer": "B"}, "Question20": {"question": "This ______ my friend. ______ name\u2019s Richard.", "example": ["A) are / His ", "B) is / My ", "C) is / His ", "D) his / His"], "answer": "C"}, "Question21": {"question": "They ______ Lisa and Max. They ______ from the USA.", "example": ["A) is / is ", "B) are / is ", "C) are / are ", "D) is / is"], "answer": "C"}, "Question22": {"question": "\u201cWhat is ______ name?\u201d \u201cMy name\u2019s Carlos.\u201d", "example": ["A) his ", "B) her ", "C) your ", "D) my"], "answer": "C"}, "Question23": {"question": "This is my sister. ______ name is Laura.", "example": ["A) His ", "B) My ", "C) Her ", "D) Its"], "answer": "C"}, "Question24": {"question": "I have ______ brother. ______ name is David", "example": ["A) an / His ", "B) a / Her ", "C) a / His ", "D) * / His"], "answer": "C"}, "Question25": {"question": "Hello! My ___ ___ Maria. I ___ ___ Mexico.", "example": ["A) name is / from am ", "B) is name / from am", "C) name is / am from ", "D) name am / is from"], "answer": "C"}, "Question26": {"question": "Is Catherine ______ sister?", "example": ["A) he ", "B) you ", "C) your ", "D) yours"], "answer": "C"}, "Question27": {"question": "We ______ students.", "example": ["A) are a ", "B) is ", "C) are ", "D) am"], "answer": "C"}, "Question28": {"question": "I ______ student.", "example": ["A) is / an ", "B) am / * ", "C) am / a ", "D) am / the"], "answer": "C"}, "Question29": {"question": "She ______ Italy.", "example": ["A) are from ", "B) is at ", "C) is from ", "D) am from"], "answer": "C"}, "Question30": {"question": "He is ______ teacher.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) * ", "D) the"], "answer": "A"}, "Question31": {"question": "I live ______ a house ______ Los Angeles.", "example": ["A) * / in ", "B) in / in ", "C) in / * ", "D) at / in"], "answer": "B"}, "Question32": {"question": "\u201c______ is your phone number?\u201d / \u201cIt\u2019s 2229\"", "example": ["A) Where ", "B) How ", "C) What ", "D) Who"], "answer": "C"}, "Question33": {"question": "\u201c______ are you?\u201d / \u201cI\u2019m Alex.\u201d", "example": ["A) Which ", "B) How ", "C) What ", "D) Who"], "answer": "D"}, "Question34": {"question": "What\u2019s this ______ English?", "example": ["A) * ", "B) in ", "C) at ", "D) on"], "answer": "B"}, "Question35": {"question": "Champaigne is ______ French drink.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) the ", "C) an ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question36": {"question": "Oxford is ______ English university.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "B"}, "Question37": {"question": "A Mercedes is ______ German car.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question38": {"question": "English is ______ international language.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "B"}, "Question39": {"question": "Milan is ______ Italian city.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "B"}, "Question40": {"question": "A JVC is ______ Japanese camera.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question41": {"question": "I have two ______ .", "example": ["A) sister ", "B) sisters ", "C) a sister ", "D) sister\u2019s"], "answer": "B"}, "Question42": {"question": "It\u2019s ______ Spanish orange.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question43": {"question": "It\u2019s ______ green apple.", "example": ["A) a ", "B) an ", "C) the ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}}